MASAHIRO NAKAMATA

Email: masahiro@nakamata.tech Portfolio: https://nakamata.tech

6 years experienced in software engineering in Tokyo. Focus on implementation, enlightenment and education for quality software design, as well as successful refactoring of legacy code. Deep understanding for design pattern and its philosophy. Invested in team building, and willing to hear and answer every level questions and opinions while staying objective.

EXPERIENCE

APRIL 2015 - MAY 2018

WEB DEVELOPER, EVERRISE CO. LTD, TOKYO

- Refined payment batch system of AD network which has over 2,000 advertisers and 45 million media including smart devices and website
- Customized PHP framework CLI for generating unit test code for a huge mobile ad network
- Implemented high traffic DMP dealing with stream processing and memory DB

APRIL 2012 - MARCH 2015

SYSTEM ENGINEER, IGUAZU, KANAGAWA(FORMERLY ALPHA COMMUNICATIONS)

- Developed POS sales management system and Inventory management for gift shops across Japan
- Dealt with and drastically changed tax rate calculation in legacy system

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2018 - CURRENT

DIPLOMA - WEB AND MOBILE APP DEVELOPMENT,

CORNERSTONE INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE, VANCOUVER

APRIL 2012 – MARCH 2015

B.A - LAW, SOKA UNIVERSITY, TOKYO

Oracle Java SE Programmer II

SKILLS

- Language
 Kotlin, Java, Swift, TypeScript
- Database
 MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Neo4j
- Framework

Angular, Play Framework, Spring Boot, Ktor

• VCS, IDE, Package Manager, Virtualization Git, IntelliJ, CocoaPods, Gradle, Maven, Docker